{
    "questions": [ 
        {
            "num": 1,
            "question": "Which of the following is not a primitive data type?",
            "answer": "String",
            "filler1": "int",
            "filler2": "double",
            "filler3": "They are all primitive"
        },
        {
            "num": 2,
            "question": "Which of the following statements assigns a random integer between 25 and 60, inclusive, to rn?",
            "answer": "int rn = (int) (Math.random() * 36) + 25;",
            "filler1": "int rn = (int) (Math.random() * 25) + 36;",
            "filler2": "int rn = (int) (Math.random() * 60) + 25;",
            "filler3": "int rn = (int) (Math.random() * 26) + 60;"
        },
        {
            "num": 3,
            "question": "What is printed as a result of executing the following statement?: System.out.println(404 / 10 * 10 + 1);",
            "answer": "401",
            "filler1": "4",
            "filler2": "41",
            "filler3": "405"
        },
        {
            "num": 4,
            "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to declare and initialize an array?",
            "answer": "int[] myArray = new int[5];",
            "filler1": "int myArray = new int[5];",
            "filler2": "myArray int[] = new int[5];",
            "filler3": "myArray[] = new int[5];"
        },
        {
            "num": 5,
            "question": "For the string str = \"Matthew Wong\", which substring method will return \"Won\"",
            "answer": "str.substring(8, 11)",
            "filler1": "str.substring(8, 10)",
            "filler2": "str.substring(7, 11)",
            "filler3": "str.substring(7, 10)"
        },
        {
            "num": 6,
            "question": "What does this equivalent to? '!(a && b)'",
            "answer": "!a || !b",
            "filler1": "!a && !b",
            "filler2": "a && b",
            "filler3": "a || b"
        },
        {
            "num": 7,
            "question": "How do you create a variable for a class? (int)",
            "answer": "private int x;",
            "filler1": "public int x;",
            "filler2": "public string x",
            "filler3": "private string x;"
        },
        {
            "num": 8,
            "question": "How do you create a json file?",
            "answer": "fileName.json",
            "filler1": "json.fileName",
            "filler2": "fileName.jason",
            "filler3": "jason.fileName"
        },
        {
            "num": 9,
            "question": "What language is this exam in?",
            "answer": "java",
            "filler1": "C++",
            "filler2": "Python",
            "filler3": "Scratch"
        },
        {
            "num": 10,
            "question": "How do you initialize a 2d array? (int)",
            "answer": "int[][] arrayName = new int[rows][columns];",
            "filler1": "int arrayName = new int[rows][columns];",
            "filler2": "String[][] arrayName = new int[rows][columns]",
            "filler3": "int[rows][columns] arrayName = new int[][];"
        }
          


    ]
}